# David Ibanez

**UI/UX** Designer

36 years old Resident visa

www.davidibanez.com dibanez@rocketmail.com Hino-shi, Tokyo-to

### **Tools**

Sketch, Adobe Creative Suite, InVision, Vs code, Tableau, Google Analytics, Google Data Studio

### **Skills**

### Design

Interface Design, Web design, user flows, Prototyping, Wireframes, Visual Design, Illustration, Design Systems

#### **User Research**

Business intelligence, Personas

### **Programing**

HTML, CSS/SASS, JQuery, React, Git versioning

## Languages

#### **English**

Business level, TOEIC: 925/990

#### **Japanese**

Business level, JLPT N2: 116/180

### 自己紹介

I'm a UI/UX designer with 8 years of experience.

My knowledge of Frontend development helps me efficiently communicate my designs to developers. I'm currently looking to join an existing design team in a company that trusts the design process to deliver meaningful and measurable changes to their customers.

# **Experience**

### **UI/UX Designer For Comvex**

Sept 2016 to present in Japan

- Worked with the Backend, Frontend team, and the production manager to conceptualized and design the new version of the company's main product.
- Improved design quality, consistency, and delivery time by creating a design system, and a documentation site for the company's main product.
- Helped improve the company decision-making process by collecting, and sharing important user and business-related metrics.

### Freelance Web Designer/Front-End-Developer

Sept 2015 to July 2016 in Japan

- Designed and developed a high-fidelity web application prototype for pharmaceutical wholesalers using AngularJS and the MEAN stack.
- Designed and developed the E-Commerce website ELSA for Salem Laboratory using Odoo EPR/CRM.
- Banding and design for OSIS a French IT service company specializing in open source technologies.

### Web Designer/Front-End-Developer For E.T.I

July 2013 to August 2015 in France

- Designed, developed, and maintained a variety of product, corporate, and E-Commerce websites as well as an in-house CMS.
- Introduce the company to modern workflows including assets optimization and automation via grunt, a custom BEM implementation via Sass.

### **Web Designer For La Bonne Agence**

May 2012 to September 2012 in France

- Designed marketing materials for Orange Music Festival, a promotional campaign organized by Orange, the world's 7th largest mobile operator.
- Designed and developed the front-end of the Nanoatschool website for MINATEC, an international campus for micro and nanotechnology research, home to 3,000 researchers, and 1,200 students.

# **Education**

### Web Design & Conception

2011 - 2012 Supcréa Design School in France

Coursework included methodology and project management, visual semiotics, graphic expression techniques, composition, typography, programming, and web design.

### **Intensive Japanese Lessons**

2009 - 2010 OLJ in Japan

Immersed in a full year of Intensive Japanese lessons 4 hours a day, 5 days a week. At the end of my studies, I was able to successfully pass the JLPT N2 test.

### **Associate's Degree In Economics And Accounting**

2007 Pierre Mendès-France Université in France

Coursework included Law Economics, Accounting, Statistics, Social Sciences, and English.